yiippee.com 2010-12-01

# Yiippee Terms

Yiippee Terms

**Yiippee Privacy Policy (Effective 22/09/2008)**

Back

Personal information is very valuable to yiippee and safe-guarding that information is very crucial to us.  
Our policy here is how we receive, collect and handle that information. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the   
services and websites offered by yiippee. 

Collection and Usage: 

Depending upon which of our services you are utilizing, the types of public personal information that we may collect include: 

To use our services for posting an Ad, you may need to register with us as a member. The member registration process   
requires that you provide your full name, email address, contact information, and other identifying information.

Based on the services, we provide you with the option to submit pictures/video and/or a description of your item or service.   
When you post an Ad on yiippee, the ad description and pictures are displayed on the site and accessible to visitors on   
yiippee. We will not post lewd, nude, or semi-nude photos, or pornographic material so please do not upload them. 

When you visit yiippee, we send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to i  
mprove the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most   
browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a   
cookie is being sent. However, some yiippee features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

Other information, including users IP address and standard web log information such as web request, browser type, the   
date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

We use users' personal information to:   
Provide our various services.

Resolve issues and troubleshoot technical problems.  

Customize users' experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates.  

Communicate marketing and promotional offers to you.  

Do other things for users as described when we collect the information. 

yiippee only processes personal information for the purposes described above. In addition to the above, such purposes include:   
Providing our services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising.

Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services.  

Provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.  

Ensuring the technical functioning of our network and  

Developing new services 

yiippee processes personal information on our servers. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside   
your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal   
information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

Using Information from yiippee: You may use personal information gathered from yiippee only to follow up with another user   
about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.

Other Websites/URLs: This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by yiippee. We do not   
exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may   
place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Public Access: The information that you provide when you post a classified ad, rate other members, and respond to ratings   
that others have given you, is posted in public areas and available to all visitors. Please remember that any information   
that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, so please exercise caution. 

Security & Disclosure   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.   
All member data and activity is stored separately and is not directly accessible through a web browser. We use industry standard   
procedures and processes to safeguard the confidentiality of your identifiable personal information, such as firewalls,   
encryption, token authentication, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our   
network and its data. Unfortunately, when you submit information about yourself to yiippee over the Internet, the information   
may travel over many systems that are not under the control of yiippee. The Internet is not 100% secure and others might   
intercept the information that you are sending. Remember that your account is accessible only through the use of your   
Password. 

Who will have access to my personal information?   
Our priority is to keep your personal information private and confidential. yiippee will not willfully disclose, rent, or   
sell your personal information to third parties. However, certain personal information will be available to others in the   
process of using yiippee. For example, visitors to yiippee may view your sign-in name, feedback rating, city, and items you   
have for sale. 

Of course, once you provide personal information to a user, yiippee has no control over how that information might be used   
by that individual. In addition, should you circumvent our on-site messaging system; yiippee will be unable to provide   
assistance in transaction disputes. We recommend using our messaging system for any communications between you and other   
potential users. 

yiippee may choose to disclose your personally identifiable information to others under the following circumstances:

You consent to share your information.   
In response to a criminal investigation, court order or legal process.

Your actions on yiippee appear to be in violation of our policies (including, but not limited to, our Terms & Conditions).  

You post a classified ad which we believe, in our sole discretion, may create a liability for yiippee.  

Nothing in this policy shall limit, prohibit, or otherwise deny the ability of yiippee to (1) transfer, assign, or sell our   
assets to a third party without limitation, or (2) dispose of our assets in any manner, through bankruptcy or similar   
proceeding. In addition, yiippee makes no warranties or claims regarding the accuracy or completeness of the information we   
collect and disclose through our site, and disclaims any liability regarding its use. 

Changes to this policy   
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without   
your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this   
page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email   
notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date,  
and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web   
site or to yiippee private. limited.

Back
